[{"date": "2018-12-19 12:08:38.804181", "chunk": 0, "question": "bicycle", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Das asf", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:08:38.804259", "chunk": 0, "question": "cat", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die asf", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:08:38.804286", "chunk": 0, "question": "dog", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Der asf", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:08:38.804308", "chunk": 0, "question": "\uace0\uc591\uc774", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die asf", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:08:38.804328", "chunk": 0, "question": "flute", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Fl\u00f6te", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:20:55.053624", "chunk": 1, "question": "\uace0\uc591\uc774", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die asf", "learned": true}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:20:55.053700", "chunk": 1, "question": "\ub9d0", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Das asf", "learned": true}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:20:55.053730", "chunk": 1, "question": "\ubc30", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Das asf", "learned": true}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:20:55.053753", "chunk": 1, "question": "\uc9d1", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Das asf", "learned": true}, {"date": "2018-12-19 11:25:55.849752", "chunk": 2, "question": "trousers", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die asf", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 11:25:55.849823", "chunk": 2, "question": "rose", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die asf", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 11:25:55.849851", "chunk": 2, "question": "trombone", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Posaune", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 11:25:55.849873", "chunk": 2, "question": "guitar", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Gitarre", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 11:25:55.849893", "chunk": 2, "question": "man", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Der Mann", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 11:25:55.849912", "chunk": 2, "question": "women", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Frau", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:20:55.053779", "chunk": 1, "question": "\ubb3c", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Das Wasser", "learned": true}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:08:38.804353", "chunk": 0, "question": "newspaper", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "Die Zeitung", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-19 12:20:55.053801", "chunk": 1, "question": "BigMac", "difficulty": 0, "answer": "BigMax", "learned": false}]